Let's try a Belly Pop.
We're going to start doing it in place, so our feet are going to be slightly apart, and one foot a little bit in front of the other one.
Our knees are going to be soft, and the motion is going to come from our belly.
We're actually going to use these muscles here and push it out.
So you want to be careful not to tilt this too much.
Okay.
You want to keep your posture nice and long and lifted.
So make sure your chest is lifted and your shoulders are relaxed.
We're going to be rocking our feet by shifting our weight front and back.
So let's start with the feet.
So it's going to go, front and back, and front and back.
And we're going to accent front and back.
So push that bell out on the front, pull it in on the back.
Push, pull in, push, pull in.
Good.
Push.
A little faster.
And push, pull in; push, pull in.
Good.
Rocking front and back.
Front, back; front, back; front, back.
Other side.
Good.
Make sure you keep that chest lifted so that all the motion is coming from right here.
So that way they can see what your body is doing.
Practice that in the mirror and make sure everything is in the right place.